

AARON OJALA

CONTACT

+358 40 514 8525 AARONOJALA@YAHOO.COM ITÄMERENKATU 34 A 32 00180 HELSINKI

PROFILE

I am a hard-working customer service specialist with a positive attitude on life. Through my past experience at working in a hectic international environment, I've learned the art of handling pressure and embracing challenges. I'm a fast learner and a person who is a team player. My goal is to continue my professional growth with new opportunities.

EXPERIENCE

SERVICE ADVISOR

FINAVIA | JAN 2018 - DEC 2019

- I worked as a Service Advisor for Finavia at the Helsinki Airport
- I was the first point of contact for passengers and companies operating at Helsinki Airport
- Assistance was given through face-to-face contact, by phone, e-mail, social media and online chat
- Main tasks included helping passengers navigate the airport, assisting in flight information and parking related matters and making announcements over the public address system

SECURITY OFFICER

AIRPRO OY | APR 2010 - DEC 2017

- I worked as a Security Officer at the Helsinki Airport
- Responsibilities included passenger and staff security at the airport's security control points and cargo luggage security screening

SHOP CLERK

K-JONTTE | 2006 - 2010

 I worked as a shop clerk for a small grocery store in Kirkkonummi

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER PROGRAM

HELSINKI BUSINESS COLLEGE | 2020 - 2021

• Studying web programming while using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React & Node.

BACHELOR OF HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT

HAAGA-HELIA UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES | 2015 - 2019

GPA: 4,38

- Studied in the English language degree programme Hospitality, Tourism and Experience Management
- Majored in Tourism Management and specialized in Transportation, Travel Agency and Event Management Business

NHTV BREDA UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES | JAN 2017 - JUN 2017

- Erasmus exchange in the Netherlands
- Studied in the degree programme of International Travel & Tourism.

FINNISH MATRICULATION EXAMINATION

ETU-TÖÖLÖN LUKIO | 2007-2010

SKILLS

- Finnish fluent
- · English fluent
- Swedish basics
- MS-office
- Windows
- Hygiene Passport